{
    "question": "Apa artinya shawty ?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "shawty itu bahasa slang-nya bhs inggris yang artinya cantik,menarik.<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "apa-beda-auxilary-amp-operator-siapa-penemu-font-old-english-907",
            "question": "-Apa beda Auxilary &amp; Operator?    -Siapa penemu font Old English?\r\n -Kapan Bahasa Inggris masuk ke Indonesia?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "gaktau ee kak bntar takcarikan yha<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bagaima-membalas-surat-kepada-pembeli-tersebut-kiara-agusta-jal-156",
            "question": "Bagaima membalas surat kepada pembeli tersebut??    kiara agusta\r\njalan W.Z Johanes No. 621\r\nThe Tiny Tots Toy Company\r\nJalan Kuningan Sari No. 50, Jakarta\r\nDear Costumer Service Respresentative,\r\n\r\nI recently purchased one of your Tiny Tents (Model #47485) for my three-year old daughter. Unfortunately, after viewing the components that came with the product, I discovered that four of the parts were missing. Also, the instructions that came with the tent are in portuguese and Russian, but not in english or french, the two languages I speak. These two unforeseen problems have resulted in the tent remeaning unassembled and unacceptable as a toy my daughter.\r\nI am writing to request replacements for the missing parts, and a copy of the full set of assembly instructions (in english or french) for the model I purchased. If reasonable arrangements are not made within ten bussines days, I will return the tent to the store I purchased it from and expect a full refund. To assist you in processing my request, I am including a copy of my sales receipt and a list of the missing parts.\r\nI have purchased other toys manufactured by your company in the past, and have always been impressed with the quality and selection that Tiny Tots has made available to its customers. I sincerely hope this is a one-time incident, and that any future purchases I make will live up to the standard my family has come to expect from your company.\r\n\r\nSincerely,\r\nKiara Agusta",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dear Kiara Agusta,<br><br>I am glad that you let us know about this matter. We are more than happy to assist you and would like to keep you impress with our service. We apologize for the missing part of the screw which supposed to be attached to the tents. We will send it tomorrow. And also the copy of the instruction will be delivered together with these missing parts. Hopefully you are satisfied with our reply and always be our loyal customer<br><br>Regards<br><br>Toytots Representative<br>Laura <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "lanjutan-jawaban-dari-in-the-developed-world-where-more-than-70-898",
            "question": "Lanjutan jawaban dari \"in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens already live in cities, urbanization is spread evenly, and population growth\" pilihan nya    a. has slowed\r\nb. would slow\r\nc. slowed\r\nd. had slowed\r\ne. will slow\r\n(simple future tense)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "d. in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens al already live in cities. urbanization is spread evenly. and population growth <u>had slowed</u>. <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "bisa saja isinya yang\u00a0<br>b. would slow, karena future pasti akan menggunakan will dan would adalah bentuk kedua dari modals tsb",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "minta-tolong-kasi-contoh-percakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pernya-886",
            "question": "Minta tolong kasi contoh percakapan bahasa inggris tentang pernyataan setuju dan tidak setuju",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Class Vacation<br><br><span>Yoga\t: So, class. Now we are going to deliberate our concern about where we are going to head for our class vacation. So, who comes up with the idea first?<br>Habibi\t: I will vote for Anyer Beach. Anyer Beach is one of the nearest beaches we can visit.<br>Yoga\t: So, class. Is there anyone who disagrees with Anyer Beach?<br>Jenny\t: Um, I am not sure about that. Last vacation our class had gone to Anyer Beach. I think we should see other options.<br>Habibi\t: Oh yeah! You\u2019re right, I forgot about that.<br>Jefri\t: Well, I\u2019m suggesting Kebun Raya Bogor<br>Kania\t: I agree with you, Jefri. I have never been there myself.<br>Geri\t: Me too, I am with you, Kania. Seeing great trees and plants must be exciting. Kebun Raya Bogor is like a great jungle in the middle of town.<br>Sarah\t: I\u2019m sorry guys. I think I will disagree with that. It\u2019s rainy season now. And as you know, Kebun Raya Bogor is located in Bogor which is the city of rain. And seeing the intensity of rainfall throughout Indonesia lately, I think we might not be able to explore the whole Kebun Raya Bogor due to the rain.<br>Tio\t: I think what Sarah said is right. Kebun Raya Bogor is not the best place to visit during this heavy rainy season<br>Yoga\t: Well, are there any other options?<br>Fauzi\t: How about Bali?<br>Habibi\t: No way! I don\u2019t have enough money to go to Bali<br>Sarah\t: Habibi is right, Fauzi. It\u2019s really costly to pick Bali as an option.<br>Yoga\t: Okay, class. To save the time, now let\u2019s just write your idea into a piece of paper and we will deliberate in the next occasion. Thank you.<br><br>contoh yang lebih simple lagi :)<br><br></span>A : hi, good morning B<br>B : morning A, how are you??<br>A : i&#039;m fine thank&#039;s<br>B : are you agree if i break up with C??<br>A : no, i don&#039;t<br>B : why??<br>A : I&#039;m not agree if you break up with C, because she more Love you then anyone, bro don&#039;t break up with her, and maybe sometime you can&#039;t find girl like C anymore, so don&#039;t break up with her<br>B : uhh, okay broooo, thank&#039;s for that<br><span>A : your welcome dude....<br></span><br>sekian dari saya :D",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Lin :I can&#039;t help to hold on any longer.<br>Sara : Oh why?<br>Lin : I think he truly never cares about me. He keeps talking about his ex-girl friend and it hurts me. He doesn&#039;t love me anymore!<br>Sara : <em>I don&#039;t think so</em>, Lin! Jey does love you so much. I know it. You&#039;re everything to him. Probably he did that just want to know how your response is. He wants to know whether you love him as he loves you. Ask him yourself and keep positive thinking. Don&#039;t ever let him go because of your emotion.<br>Lin : <em><strong>I think you&#039;re right</strong></em>. It might be better to talk to him directly. Thanks, Sara.<br>Sara : you are very welcome.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-expression-suggestion-170",
            "question": "Contoh dialog expression suggestion?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I have been usiung asparagus extract ( 2capsules per day in the morning ) on the suggestion of my doctor who is aDO.<br>This has helped reduce the amount of fluid retention. Seacoast vitamins has consistently had the lowest price for the same brand I was buying at the heralthfood store.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-perbedaan-antara-simple-past-tense-dengan-present-perfect-ten-100",
            "question": "Apa perbedaan antara simple past tense dengan present perfect tense ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple pastanse untuk menyatakan kejadian yang sudah lalu<br>present perfect untuk menyatakan kejadian yang direncanakan",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "simple past tense dipakai saat keterangan waktunya sudah selesai, \nsedangkan present perfect dipakai saat keterangan waktunya belum \nselesai/masih berlanjut.<br>Contoh:<br>I bought 3 books last week. (simple past-last week sudah berlalu)<br>I have bought 3 books this week. (present perfect-this week belum berlalu, masih berlangsung)<br><br>present perfect menggunakan &#039;for&#039; dan &#039;since&#039; saat kegiatannya masih berlanjut.<br><br>I have lived in London for 3 years. (present perfect-masih berlangsung, sekarang pun masih di London)<br>I have lived in London since 1990. (sampai sekarang masih tinggal di London)\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256",
            "question": "Pengertian dan contoh adverb of frequency",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "adverb yang menggambarkan frekuensi seseorang melakukan suatu pekerjaan, misalnya setiap hari, atau beberapa kali dalam 1 bulan<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "pengertian\u00a0: kata keterangan yang menyatakan seberapa sering suatu kegiatan yang dilakukan.",
                    "attachments": [
                        "answer-attachments/pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256-1.gif"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "create-chained-conditional-sentences-of-type-2-10-sentences-co-759",
            "question": "create chained conditional sentences of type 2 (10 sentences). continue the previous sentence with all the things in your dreams.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "If I knew you, I would marry you<br>If I married you, I would be happy<br>If I were happy, I would build a house<br>If I built a house, I would live together with you<br>If I lived together with you, I would have a nice dream<br>If I had a nice dream, I would dream about you<br>If I dreamed about you, I would live happily<br>If I lived happily, I would do everything for you<br>If I did everything for you, I would do whatever you want<br>If I did whatever you want, I would die together with you soon<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "did-he-has-a-bad-seat-203",
            "question": "Did he has a bad seat?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "dia memiliki kursi yang buruk?",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ini merupakan idiom dari suatu kondisi yang kurang nyaman pada perusahaan<br>contoh lain adalah\u00a0<br>His job is kind of hand wringing profession.<br>Pekerjaan dia adalah pekerjaan yang kadang meremas dirinya.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}